<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Irvington Voice</title>
	<atom:link href="https://ihsvoice.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://ihsvoice.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 01:49:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://ihsvoice.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/cropped-Screen-Shot-2017-02-13-at-4.42.03-PM-1-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Irvington Voice</title>
	<link>https://ihsvoice.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image>
	<item>
		<title>Features</title>
		<link>https://ihsvoice.com/features-void/2020/04/01/features/</link>
					<comments>https://ihsvoice.com/features-void/2020/04/01/features/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Features]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ihsvoice.com/?p=15917</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img src="https://ihsvoice.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/tsedhrfg.png" alt="" class="wp-image-16075" width="4555" srcset="https://ihsvoice.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/tsedhrfg.png 1501w, https://ihsvoice.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/tsedhrfg-300x226.png 300w, https://ihsvoice.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/tsedhrfg-900x679.png 900w, https://ihsvoice.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/tsedhrfg-768x579.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1501px) 100vw, 1501px" /></figure>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://ihsvoice.com/features-void/2020/04/01/features/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PRESIDENT BLUMBERG BUYS MARS: WHAT DOES THIS MEAN FOR HUMANITY?</title>
		<link>https://ihsvoice.com/news-void/2020/04/01/president-blumberg-buys-mars-what-does-this-mean-for-humanity/</link>
					<comments>https://ihsvoice.com/news-void/2020/04/01/president-blumberg-buys-mars-what-does-this-mean-for-humanity/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pingu Lamb, YouTube Commentator]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 07:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ihsvoice.com/?p=15939</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[President Mike Blumberg, former shareholder of the moon and CEO of Apple Inc., recently bought Mars on April 69th in addition to his growing collection of extraterrestrial planets. His recent purchase of Mars has been met with controversy due to the famous painter, Ellen Musk, having called dibs on owning the planet first, and many...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>President Mike Blumberg, former shareholder of the moon and CEO of Apple Inc., recently bought Mars on April 69th in addition to his growing collection of extraterrestrial planets. His recent purchase of Mars has been met with controversy due to the famous painter, Ellen Musk, having called dibs on owning the planet first, and many are worried about the precedent that this purchase sets for other planets in our solar system, including Pluto.</p>



<p>	Blumberg’s purchase of Mars is a direct result of the mental toll that his presidential campaign has put on his mind, due to his campaign not giving him enough time to satisfy his primal craving for investing in fracking in different countries as well as the criticism that he received for his communist reforms.</p>



<p>	“I needed a way to prove to the haters that I was capable of owning something worth more than them and their worthless opinions,” explained Blumberg. “I can’t believe that they called me a hypocrite for trying to introduce communist reforms just because I’m worth a quadrillion dollars! I’m going to teach these people a lesson by sending them to the gulags that I’m going to build on Mars!”</p>



<p>	However, despite these reasonable claims, Blumberg’s Mars purchase still drives concern amongst many critics. Blumberg’s mental health and intentions for humanity have always been under question, especially due to the infamous incident that occured last year in an interview on live television, in which he repeated his slogan “Mike will get it done,” for several hours without a shirt on, all the while smashing globes, ripping apart maps, and taking special care to make sure that Italy was fractured into smithereens. As a result, many believe that Blumberg’s intention with his purchase was to move to Mars in order to build a weapon of mass destruction that would annihilate the Earth.</p>



<p>Will Smuth, a well respected sports analyzer, has been especially vocal about these concerns, claiming that Blumberg’s purchase of Mars is the beginning-of-the-end of humanity, and that it was proof that capitalists should have been given the Dementor’s Kiss centuries ago. However, writers at Void, as well as other news outlets, were not able to get in touch with Smuth, due to Smuth seemingly disappearing off the face of the Earth ever since his invitational visit to the White House from Mike himself.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Blumberg responded to these concerns as well as the haters accusing him of turning on his homie Ellen Musk by beating Musk to buying out Mars first in an effort to prevent Congress from giving him an impeachment trial, along with paying those members of Congress an undisclosed amount of money.</p>



<p>“You know, I didn’t think that my homie Musk, or Muskie as I like to call him, would be too pressed,” said Blumberg. “And guess what; he wasn’t! He just said ‘Ayo, watch out, you’re going to get a surprise in your sleep one day’ which is such a nice thing to say!”</p>



<p>The consequences of President Blumberg’s purchase of Mars remain to be seen, since leading experts that estimate the economic and social impacts that this purchase will have have all mysteriously disappeared off the face of the Earth. However, the one thing this purchase proves is that no matter the adversity, and no matter the moral barriers standing in his way, Mike will get it done. <br></p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://ihsvoice.com/news-void/2020/04/01/president-blumberg-buys-mars-what-does-this-mean-for-humanity/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Irvington Administration to Install Microphones into Bathroom Stalls</title>
		<link>https://ihsvoice.com/news-void/2020/04/01/irvington-administration-to-install-microphones-into-bathroom-stalls/</link>
					<comments>https://ihsvoice.com/news-void/2020/04/01/irvington-administration-to-install-microphones-into-bathroom-stalls/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pill Weng, Staff Writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 07:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ihsvoice.com/?p=15936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In last week’s press conference on March 13, the Irvington school administration announced that they would be installing microphones into bathroom stalls for security purposes. The head of the administration said that they will continue their surveillance reinstallment program that they had started last year with the new digital clocks. “We want students to be...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In last week’s press conference on March 13, the Irvington school administration announced that they would be installing microphones into bathroom stalls for security purposes.</p>



<p>The head of the administration said that they will continue their surveillance reinstallment program that they had started last year with the new digital clocks.</p>



<p>“We want students to be safe in the event of a lockdown, fire, or other natural disasters,” said principal Aumbalnda Mneallzbbie during the meeting. “We want to know exactly where they are at any time and know that they are okay.”</p>



<p>The administration refrained from disclosing where exactly in the bathrooms the microphones would be installed, but speculation from secondary sources has suggested that they will be installed underneath toilets’ seats.</p>



<p>When asked for the inspiration for this new project, Mneallzbbie stated that they were simply continuing what they had been doing before.</p>



<p>“Our first step was with the microphones in the digital clocks,” said Mneallzbbie. “Since then we’ve made more progress by implementing teacher body cams, mandatory ankle monitors, and new prison guards to ensure that students exit the classroom with a hall pass.”</p>



<p>During the press conference, the administration also stated that microphones would come with other benefits too. In other schools where this has been done, teachers have been able to conduct several drug busts, confiscating vapes, weed, and other substances.</p>



<p>Mr. Snich, a teacher from another school who has done the same thing, is a teacher who has benefited from his school’s microphones.</p>



<p>“Before our school decided to install the microphones, I could never send kids to juvenile detention centers because I could never get any evidence, but I always suspected that my students were doing drugs in the bathrooms,” said Mr. Snich. “After they were installed, I’ve been able to catch numerous students red-handed that should’ve been suspended a long time ago.”</p>



<p>To conclude the conference, the administration announced plans to bring in guard dogs and place barbed wire along the fence surrounding the school.<br></p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://ihsvoice.com/news-void/2020/04/01/irvington-administration-to-install-microphones-into-bathroom-stalls/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
